Founder's Festival
Kibitou High School
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]（アナウンス）ただいまより
第５８回創設祭を開催いたします
The 58th Founder's Festival will now begin.
Welcome.
（生徒Ａ）いらっしゃいませ
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome.
≪（生徒Ｂ）おめでとうございます
（はるか）わおッ
Congratulations!
Wow!
（紗江）ああ　ロミオ
どうして　あなたはロミオなの
Oh, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
（美也）お～ッ　ジュリエ～ッ
Oh, Juliet!
どうして君は
ジュリエ～ッなんだ～
Wherefore art thou Juliet?!
（観客が笑う）
Oden
Girls
Swim
Club
（逢）お待たせしました
卵に　はんぺん　がんもどきですね
Here you go!
Boiled egg, fish cake and ganmodoki, right?
TL note: Ganmodoki is deep fried tofu with some other vegetables in it.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
（生徒Ｃ）部長　代わります
あッ
Captain, we'll take over.
部長も休憩行ってください
You should take a break, Captain.
ありがとう
それじゃ　お願いね
Thanks.
I'll leave it to you, then.
（手に息を吹きかけている）
I wonder if Senpai's working hard at the training camp.
先輩　合宿頑張ってるかな…
（鐘が鳴る）
Winter Training
Extra Mock Examination
Mock
Examination
Last year was so much fun.
〈去年は楽しかったな〉
〈一緒に　おでん屋台やって
一緒に温泉行って〉
We ran the Oden stall together...
...and went to the hot spring together...
やだ　私…
Oh no...
〈いつの間に　こんなに
弱くなっちゃったんだろう…〉
Since when did I become so weak?
先輩…
Senpai...
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
SS
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
Nanasaki Ai
2nd Half
Escape
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]（アナウンス）以上をもちまして
第５８回創設祭は終了いたします
And with that, the 58th Founder's Festival comes to an end.
（美也）お疲れ～
Good work!
お疲れさま
Good work.
Good work!
お疲れさま～
Yeah.
２人とも　すごく似合ってる
The two of you really matched each other!
にししッ　でしょ
全ては紗江ちゃんのおかげだね
I know, right?
It's all thanks to Sae-chan.
そんな　逆に
ギリギリまで　かかっちゃって
More like I feel sorry for taking until
the last minute to get the hang of it...
申し訳ないなって
そんなことないよ→
That's not true at all.
すっごく評判よかったし
Everyone loved it!
Thank you! Thank you all!
≪（紗江）ホント？
≪（美也）うん
R-Really?
Thank you all so much!
Yeah.
Sorry I couldn't help you guys out with the play.
ごめんね　劇の手伝いできなくて
全然　逢ちゃん　水泳部の部長の
お仕事で忙しかったし
Don't worry about it.
You're busy with your work as the Swim Club captain.
美也こそ　おでん屋台の手伝い
できなくてごめんね
I'm sorry myself for being unable
to help you out with the Oden stall.
ううん　気にしないで　１年生が
しっかりやってくれたから
No, don't worry about it.
The freshmen worked really hard.
そっか　それならよかった
I see.
That's good, then!
そうだ　これから紗江ちゃんちで
お泊まりパーティーするんだけど
I know!
We're having a sleepover party at Sae-chan's place tonight.
逢ちゃんも来ない？
えッ？
Ai-chan, wanna come too?
いいよね　紗江ちゃん
うん
You don't mind, Sae-chan?
Yeah.
来てくれると私も嬉しい
I'd be happy if you came too.
でも…
But...
そうしようよ　逢ちゃん
You should come, Ai-chan!
じゃあ　そうしよっかな
I guess I will, then.
よしッ　じゃあ決まり！
All right, it's decided, then!
（美也）ううッ　さっぶ～
早く紗江ちゃんち行って→
Ooh, it's so cold!
Let's go straight to Sae-chan's place for the sleepover party.
お泊まりパーティーしよう
（紗江）うん
Yeah.
そういえば　お泊まりパーティー
って何するの？
By the way, what are we doing at the sleepover party?
えっとね　まずはゲーム大会でしょ
次に　おしゃべり大会
Let's see...
We'll probably start with a game competition.
Then we'll have a chat competition...
それから　まんま肉まん大会
（逢・紗江）フフッ
And then we'll have a meat bun competition!
大会ばっかり
にっしっし～
Nothing but competitions.
あッ
うん？
どうしたの？
ごめん　用事を１つ忘れてた
What's wrong?
Sorry, I forgot something important.
えッ？
最近
I was so busy with morning training and Founder's Festival preparations recently that I forgot to buy Ikuo's present...
朝練とか創設祭の準備とかで
郁夫のクリスマスプレゼントを
買い忘れて…
すぐに買って郁夫に渡してくる
それからでいいかな？
I'll go buy it and give it to Ikuo straight away, so can we start after that?
うん　いいよ
待ってる
Yeah, sure.
We'll be waiting.
ありがとう
Thanks!
Shopp
ing
District
Sale
Café
《（純一）次の楽しみは　やっぱ
クリスマスイブのデートかな》
The next thing I'm looking forward to is probably our Christmas Eve date.
《はい　私も楽しみです》
Yes, I'm looking forward to it too.
あッ…
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
This is the same toy as last year.
〈これ　去年の
あのときのと同じものだ〉
《いくぞ
次は　さらに必殺技だ！》
Here we go!
It's time for your signature attack!
《へん～しん！》
《今だ！》
Transform!
Now!
《[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]マスクサンダーキック！》
Mask Thunder Kick.
フフッ
For Ages 6
and Over
Half Price
It moves!
It lights up!
It makes noise!
Flip the 3 Levers
and Kick!
Inago Mask
Action Belt
Oh no, not again...
〈やだ　また…〉
〈先輩と一緒にいられないことが
こんなにも寂しいなんて〉
It feels so lonely to be forced apart from Senpai...
What'll happen to us once Senpai goes to university?
〈先輩が大学に行っちゃったら
私達　どうなるんだろう…〉
≪懐かしいな　イナゴマスクの
アクションベルトじゃないか
How nostalgic!
Isn't that the Inago Mask action belt?
えッ？
ハア　ハア　ハア　ハア
ハア　ハア　ハア
変身ポーズ　まだ覚えてる？
Do you still remember how to do the Transform pose?
先輩…
Senpai...
あッ　どうして
ここにいるんですか　合宿は？
Wh-Why are you here? What about training camp?
抜け出してきた
えッ？
I sneaked out.
あッ　ちゃんと
今日の分は　やってきたよ
I finished all of today's stuff, though!
模擬テストだったんだけど
全部の科目を受けて
We had our mocks and I did all the
subjects and wrote down my answers.
答えも書いてきた　ただ…
It's just...
ただ？
何ていうか…
Just?
How should I say this...
どうしても七咲に会いたくなって
ガマンできなくてさ
I wanted to see you so badly, I just couldn't stop myself.
ムチャしますね
アハッ　ハハハ…
You're crazy.
だからさ　約束どおり
クリスマスイブのデートしようよ
So, like we promised, let's have our Christmas Eve date.
あッ…
何　もしかして都合悪かった？
What's wrong? Do you already have something else?
実は…
Actually...
（呼び出し中）
Hello, this is Nakata.
[TEL]（紗江）はい　中多です
もしもし　中多さん？　七咲です
Hello, Nakata-san? This is Nanasaki.
[TEL]（紗江）逢ちゃん
[TEL]（美也）逢ちゃん？　代わって
Ai-chan...
Ai-chan? Lemme speak to her.
もしもし　逢ちゃん
お買いもの終わった？
Hello, Ai-chan?
You finished shopping?
こっちは　もう準備万端だから
逢ちゃんも早く来てね
We're geared up and ready to go here, so come over soon!
[TEL]ハッハハハハハ　七咲逢は
I, the phantom thief, have taken Nanasaki Ai!
[TEL]この怪盗紳士が預かった
えッ？
先輩…
S-Senpai!
残念だが　七咲は今夜
君達のところへは行けない
Unfortunately, this means Nanasaki
won't be going to your place tonight.
悪く思うなよ
Don't be too upset.
[TEL]ハーッハハハハ　ハーッハハハ
（電話が切れる）
どうかした？
What... happened?
よっし！
よくやった　にぃに！
All right! Well done, Nii-nii!
えッ　美也ちゃん？
Miya-chan...?
あッ　ああ　ごめんね紗江ちゃん
Oh, sorry, Sae-chan.
逢ちゃん来られなくなっちゃった
えッ？
Ai-chan can't come anymore.
何か分かんないんだけど
お兄ちゃん
I don't really know how, but it looks like
Nii-nii came back from the training camp.
合宿所から帰ってきたみたいでさ
そうなんだ　それじゃ仕方ないね
I see.
It's too bad, then.
先輩　どうしてあんなこと…
Senpai, why did you do that?
ちょっとイタズラ心が
芽生えちゃって　つい
I just felt like playing a prank, so I did.
ついって…
That's your reason?
ヘッヘヘヘヘヘ
ホントに仕方のない先輩ですね
Seriously, you're such a hopeless upperclassman.
（郁夫の寝息）
メリークリスマス
Merry Christmas.
お待たせしました
待ってないよ　これでバッチリ？
Sorry for making you wait.
It's no problem.
Is that everything?
はい
じゃあ　行こっか
Yes.
Let's go, then.
はい
Okay!
やっぱり
すごく　にぎやかだね
There's a lot of people out tonight.
年に一度のイベントですから
This event only happens once a year, after all.
うんッ　何？
えッ？
What's up?
いえ　先輩とこんなふうに
イブの夜をすごせるなんて
Well, I wasn't expecting to get to spend Christmas Eve together with you, so this feels like a dream.
思ってもみなかったから
何だか夢のようで
僕もだよ
Me too.
（風が吹く）
ハックション！
先輩
Senpai!
アハハハ　慌てて出てきたから
上着を忘れちゃった
I rushed to leave, so I forgot my coat.
あッ　すみません　気がつかなくて
じゃあ私のコートを…
Sorry I didn't notice until now.
Um, take my coat...
ああ　大丈夫だよ
でも…
Nah, it's fine.
But...
どこかの店に入って
あたたまれば…
We can just go into some store and warm up...
おッ　あそこの店にしよう
さあ　行こう
Ah, let's go into that one!
Come on.
あッ　でも　あそこは…
Ah, but that's a...
うん　よく似合ってる
あの　これ…
Yup, it looks great on you!
U-Um, this...
実は塾に通う途中で
そのコートを見つけたんだ
Truth is, I saw this coat on my way to cram school.
ずっと　七咲に似合いそうだなって
思っててさ
I've always thought that it'd look good on you.
だから　これは僕から七咲への
クリスマスプレゼント
So let's make this my Christmas present to you.
でも　そんな…
But...
塾で会えなかったりしたからね
受け取ってよ
We couldn't see each other much because of cram school.
So go ahead and take it.
そうしてくれた方が
僕としても嬉しいし
It'd make me happy, too.
はい　ありがとうございます
先輩　私　大切にします
Okay, thank you.
Senpai, I'll really treasure it!
うん
じゃあ
Okay.
In that case, I'll get you a coat as your present.
先輩の上着は
私がプレゼントします
いや　いいよ　そんなの
そうはいきません
No, you seriously don't have to.
You can't do that.
この大事な時期に
カゼでもひいたら大変です
You can't afford to catch a cold at such an important time.
あッ　じゃあ　これ貸してよ
えッ　でも…
Oh, then I'll borrow this.
Eh? But...
いいから　いいから
It's fine, it's fine.
うん　あったかい
どう　似合う？
Mmh, it's really warm!
Well? Does it look good?
フフッ　フフフフ…
あれッ　ダメ？
いえ　すみません
Huh? It doesn't?
Uh, sorry.
そうじゃなくて
That's not it.
フフフフ…
ハハハハ…
≪（店員）ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
さて　それじゃ　どこ行こうか？
そうですね…
Now then, where should we go?
Let's see...
（梅原）何でだ…
Why?
何で俺に
彼女ができないんだ～！
Why can't I get a girlfriend?!
ううッ　このままじゃ
At this rate, all three years of my high school really will be devoid of color.
本当に俺の高校３年間は
灰色のままだぜ…
うんッ　あれッ？
Huh?
あいつ
塾の合宿に行ってるはずじゃ…
Isn't he supposed to be in cram school training camp?
≪（教官）ああ　ちょっと失礼
はい？
Ah, excuse me.
Yes?
この人を見かけませんでしたか？
Have you seen this person?
あっれ～　さっき
どっかで見かけたような…
Oh? I think I saw him not too long ago...
本当ですか？
何したんですか？　こいつ
Really?
So why are you looking for him?
塾の合宿所から逃げ出したのです
それで　どこで見かけましたか？
He sneaked out of cram school training camp.
So where did you see him?
えっと…　ああ　あっち
Let's see...
Ah, over there.
そうですか　ありがとう
いえいえ
I see. Thank you.
No problem~
フッ
〈（梅原）大将　これは俺からの
クリスマスプレゼントだぜ〉
Boss, this is my Christmas present to you.
よ～しッ　俺も負けてらんねえ
All right, I can't lose either!
うん？　おねえさ～ん
今　おヒマですか？
Oh, hey girl!
You free tonight?
逢ちゃん　今頃何してるかな？
I wonder what Ai-chan's doing right now.
何してるんだろうね
I wonder, too.
こっちも負けないくらい
盛り上がらないとね
We'll need to have just as much fun as her!
Yeah.
うん
というわけで…
With that said...
えッ？
まんま肉まん大会　開始～！
It's time to start the meat bun competition!
あッ
ウフフッ
フカフカ攻撃～
Soft and fluffy attack!
美也ちゃん　何でこんなこと…
Miya-chan, why are you doing...?
だって　ご利益欲しいんだもん
それにしても本当に大きいな
Well, I want to get something out of this, too!
They're seriously really big, though.
紗江ちゃん　このボリュームの何割か
クリスマスプレゼントで美也にくれない？
Sae-chan, can you split some of it with me as my Christmas present?
そんなこと言われても…
それは無理
I-It's not like I could even if I wanted to!
（美也）つれないこと言わないでさ
Don't be such a killjoy!
だって…　無理なものは無理→
But... what you want isn't... possible!
Why not? Why not?!
あんッ！
ああ　楽しかった
はい
Ah, that was fun!
Yes, it's been a while since I went all out!
久々に思いっきり遊べました
さてと　次はどこ行こうか？
All right, where should we go next?
そうですね　どこ行きましょう
Yes, where shall we go next?
ところで…　ここ　どこですか？
By the way, where are we?
えッ　うん？
Versailles
いッ　えッ？
七咲　別にワザと
こんなところに…　えッ？
Nanasaki, I didn't bring you here on purpose...
Nanasaki?
七咲？
あのさ　七咲…
H-Hey, Nanasaki...
はい…
Yes...
（麻耶）あ～ッ　すっきりした～
Ahh, that felt great!
おッ
あッ…
橘くん？
Tachibana... kun?
Crap, let's run!
まずい　逃げよう！
先輩！
S-Senpai!
ちょっと待ちなさい
Hey, wait!
≪そこのお嬢さん
お嬢さん？
Hey there, young lady!
"Young"?
は～い
お茶しません…
Yes?
Wanna have tea...
あッ…
（風が吹く）
（純一・逢）ハア　ハア　ハア　ハア
ハア　ハア　ハア　ハア
ハア　ハア　ハア
ハア　ハア
ハハハハッ
ハハハハハハ…
ハハハハハ…
ハハッ　ハハハハッ
ああ　ビックリした
Man, that really surprised me!
でも　かえって
忘れられない思い出になりました
At least it'll be a memory you'll never forget.
そうだね　一生忘れられそうにない
Yeah.
I don't think I'll ever forget it.
キレイ
うん
It's so pretty.
Yeah.
あッ
雪…
It's snowing...
私…
うん？
I...
寂しかった…
...felt really lonely.
During the time I couldn't see you, I felt really lonely...
先輩と会えない間　すごく寂しくて
I felt really afraid.
すごく不安になりました
うん
Yeah.
いつの間に私は　こんなに
弱くなっちゃったんだろうって
I was wondering how I'd become so weak...
先輩が大学に行ったら
どうなっちゃうんだろうって
As well as what would happen to us if you were to go to university...
そんなことばっかり考えて…
I couldn't stop thinking about those things...
変わらないよ　僕が大学に行っても
何も変わらない
Nothing would change.
Even if I went to university, nothing would change.
僕は七咲のことが好きだ
それで　きっと
I love you, Nanasaki.
And I'm sure I'll grow to love you even more.
もっと好きになって…
ずっと一緒だ
We'll always be together.
先輩…
Senpai...
あッ　でも明日には合宿所に
戻らないといけないだろうからな
Oh, but I'll have to go back to the training camp tomorrow.
いつも一緒っていうのは…　う～ん
So about always being together...
でしたら　私がお弁当を作って
合宿所まで　こっそり届けます
In that case, I'll make you a bento and go to the training camp to secretly give it to you.
ホントに？
はい
Really?!
Yes!
あッ　でも　もしバレたら
教官だけじゃなくて
Ah, but if they found out, it wouldn't be just the instructors who'd give me a hard time.
他の人達にも　にらまれちゃうな
怖いんですか？
全然
Are you afraid?
Not at all!
むしろ
周りの人達に自慢しちゃうね
More like I'll feel proud of myself!
アハハハハ　ハハハッ
あのさ
はい
Hey.
Yes.
Once I start university, I actually intend to
rent an apartment and start living by myself.
実は大学に受かったら
アパートを借りて
１人暮らしをするつもりなんだ
それで
もしよかったら　その…
And... if you don't mind... well...
Could you hold on to a key to my apartment?
僕の部屋の鍵
七咲が１つ持っててくれないか？
えッ　いいんですか？
Are you sure?
七咲さえ　よければ
If you don't mind, that is.
I'll be coming every morning to wake you up.
そのときは毎朝　先輩のことを
起こしに行ってあげます
うん
Yeah.
先輩　起きてください
うん？
Senpai, wake up.
Huh?
もうすぐ
花火が上がっちゃいますよ
It's almost time for the fireworks.
えッ　もうそんな時間？
What?! It's time already?
おッ　上がった上がった
時間ピッタリ！
Ooh, there it goes!
Just in time!
Senpai, you're way too excited.
先輩　はしゃぎすぎです
何だか子供みたいですよ
You're just like a kid.
そうかな？
ええ　大きな子供です
R-Really?
Yes, a big kid.
アハハハハッ
あッ
キレイですね
Isn't it pretty?
うん　そうだね
Yeah, it is.
私　来年も再来年も
I want to watch the fireworks together with you next year, the year after and forever after that.
そのあとも　ずっとこうして
２人で花火が見たいです
僕もだよ
先輩
Me too.
Senpai.
これからも
よろしくお願いします
Please continue to take care of me.
こちらこそ
Same here.
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, Nii-nii.
ねえ　にぃに　夏休み
何か初めての体験とか考えてる？
Have you thought about having a
first experience during summer break?
はあッ？　突然
何を言いだすんだよ
Huh? Wh-What on Earth
are you talking about?!
Eh? I was just asking if you were thinking of
trying a new activity like diving or fishing this summer.
えッ？　今年の夏は
ダイビングとか釣りとか
やってみたいと思わないのかなと
そっちか　脅かさないでくれよ
That's what you meant?
Don't surprise me like that.
What? I'm more surprised
with how you reacted.
みゃーは　にぃにの
驚きぶりにビックリだよ
I was thinking of traveling
somewhere this summer.
夏は旅に出ようかと
思ってるんだ
Oh, and where is Nii-nii
headed for on his trip?
そんな　にぃにの夏は
どこへ向かうのか？
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru
1st Half
Sketch
Next episode: "Sketch".
うんッ　１人旅なの？
What? You're going on your own?